I noticed something interesting as I was
looking into the South Sandwich Islands
near Antarctica. I want to draw your
attention to the third island from the
top here called Candlemass Island. And
when you zoom in, take a look at the
names of the geographical areas of the
island. Here you can see Mount Andromeda
and Gorgon Pool, Medusa Pool, Demon
Point, Vulcan Point. very peculiar that
uh they would use these names in this
location because this area viewed from
above does look like the head of a
gigantic snake or dragon which has led
some people to believe that this is an
ancient Titan or Leviathan. So, let's
take a closer look because there's even
more to this island than what is shown
on the map. You can see there is Mount
Andromeda,
but there's also Mount Perseus and
Lucifer Hill. Not to mention Demon
Point, Kraken Bay, Chimera Flats, Gorgon
and Medusa Pools, and wouldn't you know
it, Sea Surpppent Cove.
Okay, so how does this all fit together?
Well, first let's look at the story of
Andromeda, which is virtually the same
story in Clash of the Titans, where
Perseus cuts the head off Medusa in
order to kill the Titanic creature from
the underworld called the Kraken or
Setus in order to save Andromeda.
And as we know, the Kraken is a
colossalized serpent creature that lives
in the ocean. Moving on to a gorgon
which was described by the Greek Homer
as being a terrifying monster or phantom
of the underworld or Hades.
Vulcan can mean volcano but is also the
god of fire. A chimera in Greek legends
is a monstrous fireb breathing hybrid
creature that has a tail like a snake's
head and sometimes depicted with dragon
wings. They also talk of clinker gulch
on Lucifer Hill. Clinker is the remnants
of a fire like ashes, embers or
charcoal. But it also means descent or
defiance. So in other words, right at
the location of what looks like the head
of a giant serpent creature, we have an
active volcanic island with a geology
that is named after legends of a titanic
snake or a sea serpent or dragon from
the underworld. that was turned to stone
by a gorgon or the head of a medusa.
Is this a coincidence? You tell me. I
have to be honest with you. The reason I
started researching this was to disprove
what I thought was misinformation, but I
don't know. You can't really see the
body of this creature. And the location
of what appears to be its eyes are not
symmetrical.
And these are islands, not sockets. It's
likely that it just looks like a snake
head. And some are saying that it's
coming back to life, but that makes no
sense to me. Just think about the size
of this thing. It would be thousands of
miles long. The troposphere in which we
live only extends to not even 20 km.
Just standing up would reach into the
exosphere.
If this thing would decide to go for a
walk, it would literally destroy the
entire world. There are no accounts of
anything turned to stone by Medusa or
petrified in any manner coming back to
life. Petrification is a permanent
state. So whether or not this anomaly in
the ocean is Levi, you can rest assured
knowing that it's very unlikely that
it's coming back to life. Let me know
what you think.